In the last several videos, we have discussed code generation for a various
在上几个视频中，我们讨论了各种
simple programming language. In this video, we are going to take a look at code
简单的编程语言。在这段视频中，我们将看一看代码
generation for more advanced feature objects. Fortunately, this dated code
生成更高级的功能对象。幸运的是，这个标有日期的代码
generation strategy for objects is really just an extension of what we've already
对象的生成策略实际上只是我们已有的策略的扩展
learned. So, everything that you learn before we're going to be using and then
学到了东西。所以，你在我们使用之前学到的所有东西，然后
there's going to be some additional things that we do specifically for objects And,
我们会特别为物体做一些额外的事情，
the important thing to know about objects is slogan that you hear. When people
关于物品，需要了解的重要一点是你听到的口号。当人们
talked about object oriented programming is this one. So if b is a subclass of a
所说的面向对象编程就是这个。所以如果b是a的子类
then an object of class b can be used wherever an object of class a as expected.
则类B的对象可以如预期的那样在任何类A的对象处使用。
So there's a substitutability property. If I have a piece of code that can work on
所以有一个替代性的性质。如果我有一段可以工作的代码
a's then it could also work on b's and any other subclass of a. What this means for
那么它也可以对b和a的任何其他子类起作用。
the, for the case of code generation is that the code that we generate for class
代码生成的情况是，我们为类生成的代码
a. So, the code that we produced for method in class a, has to work unmodified
a.因此，我们为a类中的方法生成的代码必须原封不动地工作
for an object to class b And to see this, keep in mind that when we compile a, when
对于类b的对象并看到这一点，请记住，当我们编译a时，
we compile class a, I, we may not even know all the subclasses of a. So, those
我们编译a类，我，我们甚至可能不知道a的所有子类。所以，那些
maybe not even have been defined yet. So, in the future some programs may come
也许甚至还没有被定义。所以未来可能会有一些节目
along. To find a subclass of a then our compiled version of a will have to work
一起去吧。要找到的子类，那么我们编译后的Will版本必须正常工作
with that new subclass. So, there really only two questions that we have to answer
有了这个新的子类。所以，我们实际上只需要回答两个问题
to give a complete description of how to generate code for objects. The first one
给出如何为对象生成代码的完整说明。第一个
is how our object represented in memory. So, we need to decide a layout and
是我们的对象在内存中的表示方式。所以，我们需要决定一个布局，
representation for objects And the second one is how is dynamic dispatch implemented
对象的表示形式，第二个问题是如何实现动态调度
so that's the characteristic feature of using objects just so we can dispatch in
这就是使用对象的特征，这样我们就可以在
the method of an object and we need an implementation of that. So, to be
对象的方法，我们需要它的实现。所以，要成为
concrete, we're going to use this little example throughout this video and I'll
混凝土，我们将在整个视频中使用这个小示例，我将
just take a moment here to, to point out some features of it. So, we have three
只要花一点时间在这里，指出它的一些特点。所以，我们有三个
classes, classes am b, and c And notice that a, is a base class and b and c both
类，类是b和c，请注意a是基类，b和c都是基类。
inherit from a, And all three classes define some attributes, some fields and
继承自，并且所有三个类都定义了一些属性、一些字段和
also some methods. Now, a couple of important features here is that notice
还有一些方法。现在，这里有几个重要的特点是，通知
that because b inherits from a, and c inherits from a, they all, they both
因为b继承了a，c继承了a，所以他们都，他们都
inherit, both of those classes inherit the attributes a, and d from class a. So these
继承，这两个类都从类a继承属性a和d。
two attributes that are defined in class a are available in class b and in class c So
类a中定义的两个属性在类b和类c中可用，因此
even though there's no mention Of a, and d in the definition say of class b. The
即使在定义中没有提到a和d，也没有提到b类。
methods in class b can still refer to those attributes. They are part of the
类b中的方法仍然可以引用这些属性。它们是
attributes of class b. They are just copied over or inherited from a. Another
类b的属性。它们只是复制或继承自a。另一个
feature of this example that I like to point out is that all of the methods refer
这个例子的特点是，我想指出的是，所有的方法都引用了
to the attribute a so actually referred into this method and this one referred
到此方法中实际引用的属性a，以及此方法引用的属性a
twice in this method and also in this method. And the significance of this is
在此方法中两次，在此方法中也是如此。这件事的意义在于
just what we discussed a couple of slides ago. For all of these methods to work
这就是我们在几张幻灯片前讨论过的。要使所有这些方法都起作用
attribute a, is going to have to live in some place and some place where all of
属性a将不得不居住在某个地方，在这个地方所有的
them can find it they generate a code run. Some particular less considered the method
他们可以找到它，然后生成一个代码运行。一些特别不太考虑的方法
f. So the method f exists in all three classes. All three classes when it runs,
因此，方法f在所有三个类中都存在。当它运行时，所有这三个类，
it will refer to attribute a, and even though the objects would be different. In
它将引用属性a，即使对象可能不同。在……里面
one case it might be running on an object and in another case on a c object. It
在一种情况下，它可能在对象上运行，而在另一种情况下，它可能在C对象上运行。它
would need to be able to find the attribute a, and so therefore the
需要能够找到属性a，因此
attribute a, has to be in the same place in each object And so, how do we
属性a必须位于每个对象的相同位置，那么，我们如何
accomplish that? Well, the first principle is the objects are laid out to in
做到这一点吗？嗯，第一个原则是把物体放在
contiguous memory. So, an object is just a block of memory. Okay with no gaps and all
连续记忆。因此，一个对象只是一个内存的挡路。好的，没有缝隙
the data for the object is stored in the words of that lock of memory. And each
对象的数据存储在该内存锁的字中。而且每个人
attribute is stored at a fixed off set in the objects. So for example, there may be
属性存储在对象中的固定偏移量集中。例如，可能会有
a place in this object for attribute a On this case it's at in the middle of the
属性a在此对象中的位置，在本例中它位于
object is in the, in the fourth position And, no matter what kind of object it is,
物体在，在第四个位置，不管是什么类型的物体，
whether it's an a. B or c objects and are example as with a we always live with that
无论是a、b还是c对象，都是示例，就像a一样，我们总是生活在这样的环境中
position so that any piece of code that refers to a, any method that refers a can
位置，以便引用的任何一段代码、引用的任何方法都可以
find can find the a attribute. Now the other thing that's important to understand
Find可以找到a属性。现在，另一件重要的事情是要理解
and this is you know slight digression from what we're talking about but it's a
你知道，这与我们所说的略有偏离，但这是一个
key aspect of code generation for object is that when a method is invoked, the
对象的代码生成的关键方面是，当调用方法时，
object itself is the self parameter. So the self parameter is the entire object so
对象本身就是self参数。所以self参数是整个对象，所以
self. When a function is involved, it will refer to the entire object so you think
赛尔夫。当涉及到函数时，它将引用整个对象，因此您认为
itself is going to be appointed to the entire object. Remember that self is like
本身将被指定给整个对象。记住，自我就像是
that this variable or this name in Java. And then the fields we refer to particular
这个变量或者Java中的这个名字。然后我们引用的字段是特定的
or the attributes of the object will refer to particular position within the objects.
或者对象的属性将引用对象内的特定位置。
So, for example, the attributes, we decided to leave it there. So here is the
因此，例如，属性，我们决定将其保留在那里。所以这里是
particular object layout used in Kuhl. So the first three words of a Kuhl object
Kuhl中使用的特定对象布局。因此，Kuhl宾语的前三个词
contain header information and every Kuhl object always has these three entries. The
包含头信息，并且每个Kuhl对象总是有这三个条目。这个
first position is a class tag and also at zero then the next word it also four is
第一个位置是类标签，也是零，那么下一个词也是四
the size of the object and then something called the dispatch pointer and then all
对象的大小，然后是称为分派指针的东西，然后是所有
of the attributes. Now the class tag is an integer which just identifies the class of
属性的属性。现在，类标记是一个整数，它只标识
the object. So the compiler will number all of the classes. So in our example we
对象。因此，编译器将对所有类进行编号。因此，在我们的示例中，我们
have three classes a, b, and c and the compiler for example might assign them the
有三个类a、b和c，例如，编译器可能会为它们分配
numbers one, two, and three. It doesn't matter what these numbers are As long as
一号、二号和三号。这些数字是什么并不重要，只要
they are different from each other. So, it doesn't have these numbers consecutively
他们彼此不同。所以它没有连续的这些数字
or anything like that The important thing is of the class tag is a unique identifier
或者任何类似的东西，重要的是类标签是唯一的标识符
for a class, each class has its own unique bit pattern that tells you what kind of
对于类，每个类都有自己唯一的位模式，它告诉您哪种类型的
class the object is And the other fields here the object size is also an integer
类，此处的其他字段对象大小也是整数
which is just a size of the object in words and the dispatch pointer. Is a
它只是以字和调度指针表示的对象的大小。是一种
pointer to a table of methods so the methods are stored off to the side and the
指向方法表的指针，以便将方法存储在旁边，而
dispatch pointer is a pointer to that table and we'll talk about this more later
分派指针是指向该表指针，我们稍后将详细讨论这一点
and then all the attributes are laid out in the sub-sequence slots in some order
然后将所有属性按一定顺序排列在子序列槽中
that's determined by the compiler so the compiler will fix and order for the
这是由编译器确定的，因此编译器将为
attributes in the class and then all the objects of that class will have the
属性，则该类的所有对象都将具有
attributes of that class in the same order. And again all of this is laid out
该类的属性的顺序相同。再一次，所有这些都被安排好了
in the continuous chunk of memory. Now, I'm ready to talk about how inheritance
在连续的内存块中。现在，我准备好谈谈遗产是如何
works. So, the basic ideas like given a layout for class a, a layout for a
很管用。所以，基本的想法就像给出一个a类的布局，一个
subclass b, so this is a subclass of a can be defined by extending the layout of a.
子类b，所以这是a的子类，可以通过扩展a的布局来定义。
So, we don't need to move any of the attribute of a, we can just add more
因此，我们不需要移动a的任何属性，只需添加更多
fields onto the end of a's layout. And so, that's going to leave the layout of a
字段放到a的布局末尾。因此，这将留下一个布局
unchanged which is a great property because this is how the position of an
不变，这是一个很好的属性，因为这是
attribute in the a object will always be the same for all the subclasses. So
对象中的属性对于所有子类将始终相同。所以
essentially, we will never, once we decide where an attribute lives in a class it
从本质上说，一旦我们决定了属性在类中的位置，我们就永远不会
will never change for any of the subclasses of that object. So b is just
将永远不会更改该对象的任何子类。所以b就是
going to be an extension of the layout of a. So, let's take a look at our example
将是a的布局的扩展。那么，让我们看一下我们的示例
here and see how that, that works. Let me just write down here a little bit about
这里，看看这是怎么回事，那是怎么回事。让我在这里写一点关于
these classes because we don't have the example on the screen. So we have a class
这些类，因为我们没有屏幕上的示例。所以我们有一节课
a, and class a, had two attributes, a, and d, okay? And it doesn't matter what their
a和a类有两个属性，a和d，好吗？不管他们做什么都无关紧要
types are or what the methods were here. We're just looking at the class names and
类型是或这里的方法是什么。我们只是在查看类名和
the names of the attributes that are defined in the class. And then we have b.
类中定义的属性的名称。然后我们就有了b。
Which inherits from a and b added a attribute b and then we had c which also
它继承自a和b，添加了一个属性b，然后我们有了c，它也
inherits from a but has no relationship to b. And class c define an attribute little
继承自a，但与b没有关系，并且类c定义了一个很少的属性
c. Alright. So, that's the structure of our example is relevant to the layout of
好的。因此，这就是我们示例的结构与布局相关
the objects. Okay. So Let's talk about the layout of class a. So, in position zero at
这些物体。好吧。那么让我们来讨论一下a类的布局。所以，在位置0的位置
all sub zero, there'll be a tag for a that will be some small integer at the compiler
全部为零，则在编译器中将有一个a的标记，该标记将是某个小整数
picks. There'll be a size of a, we'll come back to that in just a se cond. There will
选择。会有一个a的大小，我们一会儿再来讨论这个问题。会有的
be a dispatch pointer again, which we're going to talk about later. And then come
再次成为分派指针，我们稍后将讨论这一点。然后就来了
the attributes of a, and it just laid out the compiler, the way it's done in the,
的属性，它只是布置了编译器，就像它在中所做的那样，
the Kuhl c implementations is that they are laid out in the order in which they
Kuhl c++实现的特点是，它们是按照它们的顺序布局的。
appear textually in the class. So, in this case, first the attribute a, And then the
以文本形式出现在类中。因此，在本例中，首先是属性a，然后是
attribute d all sets twelve and sixteen And now since the object, there are two
属性d全部设置为12和16，现在由于对象，有两个
attributes and three header words that means the size of the object is five words
属性和三个标题字，这意味着对象的大小是五个字
and so it's a five that goes in the size field for a objects. Now, let's take a
所以它是一个5，在物体的大小字段中。现在，让我们来看一看
look at b. Okay? So b is going to have a different tag, b objects will have a
看看b，好吗？所以b将有一个不同的标记，b对象将有a
different tag so they to distinguish them from a objects. There's going to be extra
不同的标签，以便将它们与一个对象区分开来。会有额外的费用
fields so the size will be one bigger But now the layout preserves the layout of a.
字段，因此大小将增大一个，但现在布局保留。
So the attributes of a appears in the same position. So you can think of there being
所以a的属性出现在相同的位置。所以你可以想象有没有
an a object Actually embedded inside of the b object. If I were to strip off the
A对象实际上嵌入在B对象内部。如果我剥去
end here that were just you know cover up this last bit here b I would say that this
在这里结束，只是，你知道，把最后一点盖在这里，b，我会说，这是
object here has the same size and the same attributes as an a object so any piece of
这里的对象与a对象具有相同的大小和相同的属性，因此任何
code that could work on an a object will also make sense running on a b object. Now
可以在a对象上运行的代码在b对象上运行也是有意义的。现在
Of course, the tag is different because it actually is a subclass and you know, and
当然，标记是不同的，因为它实际上是一个子类，而且
there is an extra field so the, the size is different but the point is that any
有一个额外的字段，所以大小是不同的，但重点是
code that it refer is just to the fields here will still work just fine. So any a
它引用的只是这里的字段的代码仍然可以很好地工作。所以任何一个
method that was compiled that refer to the methods of an a object will still find
引用对象的方法的已编译方法仍将找到
those attributes in the same place at the b object and afterwards, there is also one
这些属性位于b对象的同一位置，之后还有一个
more field here. Which is the new attribute b It just gets laid out after
这里有更多的场地。这是新的属性b，它只是在以下位置布局
all of a's fields. So after all of a's fields come all of b's fields in the same
所有a的字段。因此，在所有a的字段之后，所有b的字段都在同一个字段中
order which they appear textually in the class because there's just only one,
它们在类中以文本形式出现的顺序，因为只有一个，
there's just one new field there. And now looking with class c or the story with
那里只有一块新的田地。现在来看c类，或者讲故事
class c is very similar so c has its own distinct tag and also has one more
类c非常相似，因此c有它自己的不同标记，并且还有另外一个标记。
attribute than a so it has size six. And now again the a attributes were on the
属性，所以它的大小是6。现在，a属性再次出现在
same position and now the c attribute just comes after the a attribute. And so notice
同样的位置，现在c属性紧跟在a属性之后。所以请注意
here that a methods again will work just fine on c objects because the attributes
在这里，a方法同样可以在c对象上很好地工作，因为属性
are on the same places and so the methods will find the attributes where they expect
位于相同的位置，因此这些方法将在它们期望的位置找到属性
to. You cannot however call a method of class b on an object to class c. Okay
致。但是，您不能将对象上的类b的方法调用到类c。
because they have different attributes in the third position. We may have completely
因为它们在第三个位置有不同的属性。我们可能已经完全
different types. It may not make sense to invoke a b method on c object but that's
不同的类型。在c对象上调用最佳方法可能没有意义，但这是
just fine because if we look at our inheritance hierarchy over here we'll see that b and
很好，因为如果我们看一下这里的继承层次结构，我们会看到b和
c are actually unrelated. They are both subclasses of a but they have no
c实际上是无关的。它们都是a的子类，但是它们没有
relationship to each other. B is not a subclass of c and c is not a subclass of b
彼此之间的关系。B不是c的子类，c也不是b的子类
and so anything beyond their shared ancestry with a can be completely
因此，任何超越他们共同祖先的东西都可以完全
different in the layout. So, more generally, if we have a chain of
在布局上有所不同。所以，更广泛地说，如果我们有一系列
inheritance relationship, so let's say, we have a base class a1 and a1 inherits some
继承关系，所以假设我们有一个基类A1，A1继承了一些
a1 and a3 inherits some a2 and so on with some class a and inheriting at the bottom
a1和a3继承一些a2，依此类推，具有一些a类，并在底部继承。
of this of this chain after some long sequence of, of other intermediate. Some
在一些长的，其他中间体的序列之后，这条链的这一部分。一些
classes, you know, what is the layout of all these classes going to look like.
课程，你知道，所有这些课程的布局是什么样子的。
Well, there's going to be a header. Okay, the three word header and that will be
嗯，会有一个头球。好的，三个字的标题就是
followed by a1's attributes. And then followed by a2's attributes followed by
后跟A1的属性。然后是a2的属性，然后是
a3's attributes and so on all the way down to an's attributes down here. Okay. And if
A3的属性，以此类推，一直到这里的An的属性。好吧。如果
you look again so what we talked about before each prefix. Of this header is
你再看一遍，我们在每个前缀之前都谈到了什么。此标头的
essentially a valid object a valid one of these objects. If I look at the first set
本质上是一个有效的对象，这些对象中的一个有效的。如果我看第一盘
of attributes, everything up to the end of a1 and attributes, that forms a valid
属性，直到A1和属性末尾的所有内容，这构成了一个有效的
layout for one object is I stop with the a2 attributes. I have a, I have a, I have
一个对象的布局是我停止a2属性。我有，我有，我有
a valid layout for a2 object going all the way from the header down to you know,
2对象的有效布局从标题一直到您知道的，
including the a1 and a2 objects. And then a3 includes all a1, a2 and a3's attributes
包括a1和a2对象。然后a3包括a1、a2和a3的所有属性
and so on. Okay? So, each prefix Of, of this object, Of this a and object has a
诸若此类。好吧?所以，这个对象的每个前缀，这个a和对象的每个前缀都有一个
correct layout for some for some super class of A n.
An的一些超类的正确布局。